Survivors will become heroes.
Forbidden Ground is a war, action, drama film directed by Johan Earl.
Three British soldiers find themselves stranded in No Man's Land
after a failed charge on the German Trenches.
Set in France 1916.
Sgt. Maj. Arthur Wilkins, played by Johan Earl.
Pvt. O'Leary, played by Tim Pocock.
Cpl. Richard Jennings, played by Martin Copping.
Grace Wilkins, played by Denai Gracie.
Eve Rose, played by Sarah Mawbey.
Dr. Bennett, played by Barry Quin.
Forbidden Ground, also known as Battle Ground in the United States, is a 2013 Australian action drama film,
starring Johan Earl, Tim Pocock, and Martin Copping, set against the backdrop of World War I.
It was written by Earl, Denai Gracie, and Travis Spiteri,
and directed by Earl and Adrian Powers.
The tone is emotional.